visitbrussels.be 2019-04-26

# Privacy policy | Visit Brussels

**visit.brussels ASBL**

Effective since: 10/09/2018

We make it a matter of pride to respect the privacy of our users and to treat their personal data in the strictest confidentiality and in accordance with the legislation in force.

The privacy policy is intended to inform you, in a transparent manner, about the data we collect, the purpose for collecting it, the way we use it and the rights you have regarding the processing of such data.

On this page, we provide you with a simplified version of our privacy policy in the form of questions and answers. We invite you to also read the detailed version available here

We draw your attention to the need to read this privacy policy carefully. If you have any other questions, do not hesitate to contact us at the following address: [dataprivacy@visit.brussels](mailto:dataprivacy@visit.brussels)

  1. **WHO IS RESPONSIBLE FOR PROCESSING YOUR DATA?**

Visit.brussels is the controller of your personal data. 

Here is our complete contact information: 

Asbl visit.brussels,   
Rue Royale 2-4  
1000 Bruxelles 

Belgian business registry (BCE) number: 0600.885.207  

  2. **WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT?**

We collect your data - personal or otherwise - for various reasons which are defined in the following point (see point 3). It includes the following data: 

  * your identifying information (surname, first name, marital status, email address, date of birth and delivery address);
  * your bank details (credit card number, IBAN and BIC/SWIFT)
  * your invoicing details;
  * our communications (by email or other);
  * the type of domain with which you connect to the Internet;
  * the IP address assigned to you;
  * the date and time of your access to our website;
  * location data or other data relating to the communication;
  * the pages you viewed on our website;
  * the type of browser, platform and/or operating system you are using;
  * the search engine and the keywords used to find the website;
  * your browsing preferences and
  * any other data that you would communicate to us.

  3. **WHY DO WE COLLECT YOUR DATA?**

We collect your data  to establish, carry out and conduct the contractual relationship with you, for the User to participate in games / contests / quiz and, in general, to provide the Service,- to incorporate users' personal data into one or more automated files, to analyze, adapt and improve the content of the Website, to carry out internal statistical surveys and market surveys and to deploy various statistical systems and studies, to allow the User to receive messages and manage his account from different devices (computer, tablet, smartphone, etc.), to detect and / or prevent fraud or similar activities of an illegal nature, to verify credit cards and other types of payment cards, to respond to requests for information, for any marketing and promotions actions offered by visit.brussels to Subscribers to the Newsletter, to inform them about the evolutions of the Website and its functionalities, to transfer the personal data of our booth visitor to our partners present on the booth, and for any other purpose for which the User has expressly consented.

to facilitate the provision and use of the Website and improve the Services offered by visit.brussels as well as the experience of the Users; The legal bases for processing your data are listed in the full version of the Privacy Policy.

  4. **HOW DO WE COLLECT YOUR DATA?**

Most of your data is communicated to us by your active intervention Other data, such as the date and time of your access to our website, the pages you have viewed, or your location data, are collected automatically through servers consulted and "cookies" placed on our website. For more information on what a cookie is, how it is used and the exact data it collects, visit our page concerning our [cookie policy](https://visit.brussels/en/article/cookies-policy). 

  5. **ARE YOUR DATA PROTECTED?**

We take pride in respecting the privacy of our users. We maintain a strict privacy policy and take all appropriate measures to ensure that our servers prevent, to the extent possible, any unauthorized leak, destruction, loss, disclosure, use, access or modification of your data. 

  6. **HOW LONG DO WE STORE YOUR DATA?**

We keep your data for the time necessary to accomplish the objectives pursued (see point 3). __ Once this goal is achieved, we delete them.

  7. **WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS AND HOW CAN THEY BE EXERCISED?**

You may, at any time, request to verify, access, rectify, delete, transfer and object to the use of your data, as well as request the limitation of such use of your data. To do so, simply send us an email at the following address: [dataprivacy@visit.brussels](mailto:dataprivacy@visit.brussels) . _We will then make every effort to take the necessary action as soon as possible._

  8. **WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR DATA AND TO WHOM ARE THEY COMMUNICATED?**

Our employees and subcontractors have access to your data only to the extent necessary for fulfilling the objectives pursued (see point 3). Each of them is subject to a strict obligation of confidentiality. The categories of recipients are listed in the full version of the Privacy Policy.

  9. **DO WE TRANSFER YOUR DATA ABROAD?**

We only transfer your data to a non-EU country if it provides a level of protection equivalent to what you can find in your country of residence (for more information, please check: <https://goo.gl/1eWt1V> ).

  10. **HOW TO RECEIVE OUR PRODUCTS ?**

With your consent or based on our legitimate interest based in particular on our relationship, we will subscribe you to our newsletter and offer you other similar products or services that may interest you. You can unsubscribe and withdraw your consent to these communications at any time by sending an email to the following address: [dataprivacy@visit.brussels](mailto:dataprivacy@visit.brussels)

  11. **WHAT IS OUR POLICY ON DATA CONCERNING MINORS?**

Our website is not targeted to children under the age of 18. If you learn that your minor child has provided us with their personal data without your consent, contact us at the following address: [dataprivacy@visit.brussels](mailto:dataprivacy@visit.brussels) .

  12. **WHAT HAPPENS IN THE EVENT OF A CHANGE TO THE PRIVACY POLICY?**

If we had to make any changes to this privacy policy, you would be notified through our website. 

  13. **WHAT TO DO IN THE EVENT OF A DISPUTE?**

Lengthy trials do not benefit anyone. In the event of a dispute between us, we commit to give priority to dialogue and openness in search of an amicable solution. You can also contact the Data Protection Authority.
